IBT Affiliate Records Department - Local Union Rosters, 1954-2010 IBT0082
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Affiliate Records Department - Local Union Rosters
1954-2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America.
IBT0082
0.5 Cubic Feet 30 rosters
The collection consists of IBT local union rosters which provide data on local union leadership and contact information.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of IBT local union rosters. Rosters list local unions numerically and regionally. The provide informatiuon on local union leadership, street addresses and telephone numbers. Joint councils are also listed.
Arrangement
The rosters are arranged chronologoically by year.
Biographical / Historical
The IBT has published local union rosters annually since the early days of the union. Besides publishing rosters, the Affiliate Records Department maintains records on local union per capita tax payments and communicates with locals on matters of charter application, issuance or revision; seal procurement, surety bond coverage and groupm tax exemption with the IRS.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was transferred to Gelman Library from the International Brotherhood of Teamsters
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor and laboring classes
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Affiliated Records Department Local Union Rosters, 2021 April; IBT0084 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 21)